



Elissandro Vieira

Nationality: Brazilian Date of birth: 04/07/1995 Phone number: (+55) 21982485926

Email address: teofiloeli@gmail.com Whatsapp Messenger: +55 (21) 98248-5926

O Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/juniorelissandro/

Website: https://github.com/elissandrovieira

ABOUT ME

I worked as a UI and Graphic Designer for the last 10 years. Last year, I fell in love with Front-end Development and since then, I worked to learn more and make me a competent professional. I'm looking for my first opportunity in the tech market, to contribute to the team and get a lot of experience.

I developed designs for brands around the world such as Sultan Tea UK (London, England), Tala Raassi (United States) YDAWI and LinkBuilding Estratega (Zaragoza, Espanha) and I want to use this experience in design on ,(Dubai, Emirados Árabes) يُدوَياً development.

PROJECTS

Second-Hand marketplace

The Second-Hand marketplace project is a used item marketplace.

User can search and negotiate items that he wants to buy, or register ads to sell items.

Used technologies:

- Next.js Front-end, Back-end
- · Mongo DB Database

Live Demo:

https://second-hand-marketplace.vercel.app/

Repository:

https://github.com/elissandrovieira/second-hand-marketplace

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end developer

Freelancer [05/2022 - Current]

I work today to develop websites, landing pages, and web apps.

art director

DDAY Creative Solutions [07/01/2018 – 29/09/2021]

City: Rio de Janeiro Country: Brazil

I was responsible for coordinating the design team in the development of branding and advertising campaigns.

UI Designer

Firefly Design [06/03/2016 - 16/01/2017]

City: Rio de Janeiro Country: Brazil

I was responsible for designing all user interfaces from the agency's internal system and for some agency's customers.

graphic designer

FREENESI DESIGN [28/11/2013 - 27/02/2016]

City: Rio de Janeiro Country: Brazil

I was responsible for designing branding and logo for agency's customers.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Web Development

Full stack Javascript training [01/07/2022 - Current]

HTML5/CSS3

Curso em vídeo [10/05/2022 – 01/07/2022] Website: https://www.cursoemvideo.com/

Technical Degree in Graphic Design

Seven Computer Graphics School [24/04/2009 – 25/10/2011]

Address: Av. N. S. de Copacabana, 605 Rio de Janeiro, RJ, 22050-902 Rio de Janeiro (Brazil)

Website: http://www.sevencg.com.br/

DIGITAL SKILLS

Web Development

HTML / CSS / Sass / Javascript / React.js / Next.js / Node.js / Express / Git / MongoDB

UI Design

Figma / Adobe XD / Sketch / Adobe Photoshop / Adobe Illustrator / Wordpress

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Portuguese

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING B1 READING B1 WRITING B2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B1 SPOKEN INTERACTION B1